thefix.com 2017-09-04

# Privacy Policy | The Fix

  1. Home

## Will My Insurance Pay for Rehab?

Submitted by Allison Floam on Fri, 03/25/2011 - 17:04 

**Last Updated: March 8, 2011**

 **PRIVACY POLICY**

The Fix (and TheFix.com) is a business of Clean & Sober Media, LLC.  The Fix respects the privacy of our users and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of The Fix or our services, or otherwise provide us with information through various means the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

 **Information we collect about you**

We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

  *  **Information you provide**. We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information.
  *  **Information from other sources**. We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from business partners, contractors and other third parties. Examples of information that we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.
  *  **Information about others.**  We may also collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us. If you use our website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a product as a gift, information that may interest them or messages (such as invitations) through our system, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient.
  *  **Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information.**  We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site.
  *  **Information collected automatically.** We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our website. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see “Cookies" below), and the referring website address.
  *  **Cookies.** When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies.
  *  **Other Technologies.** We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.
  *  **Information collected by third parties.** We may allow third parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies (www.networkadvertising.org).

 **How we use the information we collect**

We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * Deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * Provide you with customer support;
  * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our partners, or other third parties;
  * Develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites;
  * Verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
  * Enforce our terms and conditions;
  * Manage our business and
  * Perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

Financial information

We may use financial information or payment method to process payment for any purchases made on our website, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

Job applicants

If your personal information is submitted through our website when applying for a position with our company, the information will be used solely in connection with considering and acting upon your application. We may retain your personal information for a period of time, but only for the purpose of considering your application for current or future available positions. This information may be shared with our partners for the purpose of evaluating your qualifications for the particular position or other available positions, as well as with third-party service providers retained by us to collect, maintain and analyze candidate submissions for job postings.

 **With whom we share your information**

We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our web site or while using our services.

Personal information. We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with:

  *  **Authorized service providers** : We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  *  **Business partners** : When you make purchases, reservations or engage in promotions offered through our website or our services, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.
  *  **Other Situations**. We also may disclose your information:
  * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
  * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.
  * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies, which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.

Aggregated and non-personal information

We may share aggregated and non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on websites of third parties. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our website and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop website content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.

 **Third-party websites**

There are a number of places on our website where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement or a search result on our website, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.

 **Your choices about collection and use of your information**

  * You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; or initiate other transactions on our website.
  * At any time you can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails  _or newsletters_  from us by unsubscribing _._ You also will be given the opportunity, in any commercial e-mail that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please note that opting out of receipt of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third party before you have changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change you preferences directly with that third party.

 **How we protect your personal information**

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. We want you to feel confident using our website to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's website at http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

 **Blogs, bulletin boards, reviews and chat rooms**  where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others as well as post reviews or upload content (e.g. pictures, videos, audio files, etc.).Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information.

 **Children's privacy**

Our website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

 **Visiting our websites from outside the United States**

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

 **No Rights of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

 **How to contact us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by e-mail or postal mail as follows:

Email: [info@thefix.com](mailto:info@thefix.com)

## Learn More About The Top Rated Rehabs In the Country

  | 

###  Visions Adolescent Treatment

Visions offers top-of-the-line treatment for 13 to 18 year old addicts, with alumni that includes Elizabeth Brockovich—daughter of Erin Brockovich—who found treatment in Vision's outpatient, day school, sober living and their Launch program. 

Rating: 5 stars

_33335 Mulholland Highway, Malibu, CA 115 Barrington Walk, Los Angeles, CA 90049_

_$40,000/30 days (45 day minimum)_  
  
---|---  
  | 

###  Cliffside Malibu

The “beach-house-relaxed” **Cliffside Malibu** claims to provide an oasis for recovering addicts and alcoholics. And that’s just what you'll get—if you’ve got the cash. 

Rating: 5 stars

_Malibu, Calif._

_$58,000/mo._  
  
  | 

###  Newport Academy

This SoCal rehab fosters a regimented but respectful recovery environment, where teens learn how to live sober through plenty of 12-step meetings and life-skills classes—not to mention "equine-assisted psychotherapy" and mixed martial arts. 

Rating: 5 stars

_Newport Beach, Calif._

_$30,000/mo._  
  
  | 

###  Sunset Malibu Treatment Center

The kind of addict who comes to Sunset Malibu is frequently using drugs to cope with a deep pain; for these people, life is just too painful to deal with without the buffer of drugs or alcohol. 

Rating: 5 stars

_Malibu, CA_

_$58,000/mo. for a semi-private room;_  
  
  | 

###  Sober College

At Sober College, young people learn life skills and can take accredited college courses while going through treatment for addiction. 

Rating: 4.5 stars

_Woodland Hills, CA_

_$15,000 - $25,000 per month;_  
  
  | 

###  AToN Center

Whether you’re interested in the 12 Steps, SMART Recovery, or holistic treatments, this luxurious, appealing and commendable 4.5 star  **San Diego rehab** has a program for you. 

Rating: 4.5 stars

_San Diego_

_$45,000 - $149,900 per month_  
  
  | 

###  Genesis House

Every Genesis alum who took our survey has remained clean and sober, with more than half of the respondents having double-digit sobriety. 

Rating: 4.5 stars

_Cheviot Hills, CA_

_$10,000 - 15,000/mo._  
  
  | 

###  Access Malibu

Access Malibu offers five-star treatment and luxury amenities at a more accessible price. 

Rating: 4.5 stars

_Malibu, CA_

_$25,000 to $34,000 per/month._  
  
  | 

###  Discovery Place

This 12-step based non-profit Tennessee facility for men offers meetings, groups, camaraderie, and boasts an impressive success rate. 

Rating: 4.5 stars

_Burns, TN_

_30-day program: $6500; LTR Program / Extended Care: $5500 (monthly); step-down program (outpatient): $1500_  
  
  | 

###  Northwest Counseling & Wellness Center

This Austin, Texas rehab provides substance abuse and mental health services as an outpatient programs. It is universally beloved by its clients and alumni for the therapy provided to the individual and the support freely given by a caring staff. 

Rating: 4.5 stars

_Austin, TX_

_$190/day_
